有事吗 小花生米
What's up, peanut?
麦克斯 我不是付钱让你白站着的
Max, I'm not paying you to just stand there.
你也没有付钱让我尽量吃
Well, you're not paying me to eat as many french fries
任何从厨房端出来的薯条啊
as I can before the plate leaves the kitchen,
但我还是吃了
but I do that too.
去招待那个美女啊
Go wait on that pretty girl.
等等 她是男的吗
Oh, wait. Is she a boy?
她看起来像个美男
She looks a little like a pretty boy.
她看到你 心里估计也想着你是小萌妞吧
She's probably looking at you and thinking the same thing.
那你是被她女孩的身份所吸引
But are you attracted to the girl she is
还是外表的男儿样所迷惑呢
or the boy she appears to be?
你自己都答不上了吧 阿憨
You're confused, aren't you, Han?
对啊 我的脑子说不行
Yes, my mind tells me one thing,
但身体好像挺老实的
but my body tells me something else.
麦克斯 去休息吧 卡座区我来
Max, go on break. I've got the booth.
不行 不能让你招待她
Oh, no. You can't wait on her.
她是缇娜 化女孩为女同的拉拉女王
That's Tina, a lesbian who turns straight girls.
我称她"掰弯者缇娜"
I call her "Tina the turner."
基本上威廉斯堡区的
Practically every heterosexual woman
每个直女都跟她有过一腿
in Williamsburg has hooked up with her.
麦克斯 每一个吗
Max, everyone?
我没有 你觉得是谁"掰弯"她的呢
Not me. Who do you think turned her?
相信我 你是挡不了她的魅力的
But you won't be able to resist her charm. Trust me.
听你在胡扯 我对自己的性向很放心
That's nonsense. I'm very comfortable with my sexuality.
我有一次还发短信支持
I once texted "Yes" to Mr. Chaz Bono
《与星共舞》的查滋·波诺呢
on Dancing with the Stars.
行 那祝你好运啦
Okay, good luck.
别等会让我抓到你们在桌上亲热
Just don't let me catch you guys making out on the table.
要也行啊 这是个自由的国家
Or do. It's a free country.
您准备好要点餐了吗
Hi, are you ready to order?
行 对了 我好喜欢你的头发
Sure. I love your hair, by the way.
厄尔 卡洛琳马上要爱上一个拉拉了
Earl, Caroline's about to fall in love with a lesbian.
真"意外" 我"完全没料到"
Well, color me "I saw that one coming."
怎么样啦
How'd it go?
还行啊 她称赞了我头发
Fine, she complimented my hair,
然后点了个汤 我把我电话告诉她
She ordered a soup, I gave her my number.
我怎么会告诉她我电话
I gave her my number?
你赶紧去洗澡准备吧
Okay, hit the showers.
这就是我让一个直女去做
That's what I get for sending a straight woman
像我这样情感已死之人工作的后果
to do an emotionally dead woman's job.
今早起床感觉太爽了
It was so nice to wake up this morning
没有经营一家小蛋糕店的压力
without the stress of owning our cupcake business.
我唯一需要做的决定是
The only decision I have to make today is:
我今天该换内裤呢
do I change my underwear
还是反过来继续穿呢
or just turn these inside out?
四年前 我也碰到过类似的难题
Four years ago, I was hit with a similar conundrum:
"是买内裤呢 还是买啤酒呢"
"Do I buy underwear or do I buy beer?"
然后就一直不穿裤衩到现在
I've been free-balling it ever since.
麦克斯 你在干嘛 你那边在搞啥呢
Max, what are you doing? What's happening over there?
你是说小店的箭头灯吗
Oh, you mean the arrow from the shop?
我放在那里好让你知道
I put it on so you'd know
羞辱你的言语来自哪里
where the insults were coming from.
我是说小蛋糕
I'm talking about the cupcakes.
我们的店都倒了
Our cupcake shop is gone.
你干嘛还继续做小蛋糕啊
Why are you still making those things?
这是我生活中唯一固定的习惯
It's the only constant in my life,
也是我每天用来忘却潜伏在我思绪中
and the routine distracts me from the relentless darkness
那无尽黑暗的方式
that lurks in every corner of my thoughts.
而且我们得在餐厅里继续卖
Besides, we still need to sell these at the diner
好赚点外快啊
to make extra money.
你要做随你 我是懒得理它们了
Well, you can do it. I'm not speaking to them.
它们根本就拐我跳坑
They totally led me on.
玩弄我又嘲笑我
Those cupcakes were a tease.
但我还想付这个月的房租
Well, I want to pay rent this month.
还有下个月 下下个月 之后所有
And then again next month, and so on and so on
直到死神哪天来放我自由
until the exquisite release of death.
房租 这婊子真烦
Oh, rent. Here we go again.
简直是没完没了啊
Does that bitch ever stop?
如果是死神 那就是找我的
If that's death, it's for me.
告诉他 到了就按喇叭 我立刻出去
Tell him to honk and I'll be right out.
早安啊 栗宝
Morning, Chestnut.
你那又大又美的双眼
Oh, what is it about those big, beautiful eyes
怎么总能够让一切变美好呢
that makes everything feel better.
可能我眼神透漏出温暖吧
I guess I just have a warmth.
你是在说马呀
Oh, you mean the horse.
这还能喝吗
Is this still good?
绝对不能了
It is not.
但我哪有得选
Eh, like I have a choice.
是我的过去打来的
Wow, that was a blast from the past-
我以前的临时工中介
my old temp agency.
有员工染流感 病倒了 他们需要人手
Flu's got their staff laid up. They need bodies.
有兴趣吗 他们会愿意一起请的吧
Wanna do it? I bet they'll let us temp together.
你觉得 你觉得他们会让我们一起咩
You think? You think they'd let us temp together?
天啊 上周
Oh, God. Last week,
我还是个小老板 现在要当临时工
I owned a cupcake business, now I'm temping.
干嘛不叫栗宝踹我脑袋一脚算了
Why don't I just ask Chestnut to kick me in the head?
他不愿意 我都求了他七次了
He won't do it. I've asked him like seven times.
起床后十分钟内 我们两个
Look, we've both casually fantasized about our deaths
都想过自己去死了
within ten minutes of waking up,
所以何不做点什么来分散思绪
so maybe we should do something to distract us.
复印东西就能让生命圆满吗
And xeroxing will make us feel whole?
让姐告诉你
Let me tell you something.
当坐在影印机上复印屁股时
when you're photocopying your ass on a xerox machine,
你会焕发前所未有的活力
you are never more alive.
你好啊 老朋友
Hello, old friend.
你看 这是我的临时工外套
Here it is, my temping blazer.
上面都还闻得到那"死路一条"的气息
Ahh, you can still smell the "no way out."
为什么它被塞水桶里啊
Why is that in a bucket?
我不想不小心穿到啊
'Cause I don't want to accidentally wear it.
那烤箱里有能借我穿的裤套装吗
Well, is there a pantsuit in the oven I could wear?
你穿啥根本无所谓 你就是个临时工
It doesn't matter what you wear--you're a temp.
你不拉屎在裤子上他们就很开心了
They'll be impressed if you don't poop your pants.
而且就算拉了 也不会炒你的
And even if you do, not a deal breaker.
好吧 我去
All right, I'll go,
但如果要开始当临时工赚房租
but if we're temping to make our rent,
那以后就不许做小蛋糕了
that's the last batch of those.
我不想再见 再听 再想
I don't want to see, hear, or think
任何小蛋糕的事情
any more about cupcakes.
叮咚 是小蛋糕
Ding dong, the cupcake's calling.
我们在楼下垃圾堆找到了你们店的
We found the cupcake costumes from your store
小蛋糕服
out near the dumpster.
-你们喝醉了吗 -没错
- Are you guys drunk? - Yes!
我们泡了整晚的夜店
Yeah, we've been out clubbing all night.
我刚不小心吞了我的一颗蛋蛋
Oh, I just swallowed one of my balls.
对啊 对啊
Yeah. Yeah.
现在你知道我的感受了吧
Well, now, you know how I feel.
我是故意丢掉那小蛋糕服的
I threw those costumes away on purpose.
我跟麦克斯以后不再做小蛋糕了
Max and I are no longer making cupcakes.
你说什么
What'd you say?
小蛋糕浪费时间浪费钱
Cupcakes are a waste of time and money.
把这话给老娘收回去
You take that back right now!
不 你不行...
No, you don't-
算你走运
You're lucky
现在有个巨型小蛋糕在拦着我
that I have a giant cake holding me back right now.
五楼 梦想终结处
Fifth floor, end of dreams.
我在这里工作过呢
Oh, yeah, I worked here before.
记得我们家厨房的烤面包机吗
You know the toaster oven in our kitchen?
就是这里搬的
It came from here.
你好 我是卡洛琳·钱宁 新人报到
Hi. Caroline Channing, reporting for my first day.
我已经打印好我的地址
I went ahead and printed out my address,
社保号码 以及其他重要资料
social security number, and other important information
以防给您造成不便
to make your life easier.
我是临时工二号 你们厕所在哪呢
Hey, I'm temp number two. Where your bathroom at?
我去叫伊莱 他是我老板
I'll get Eli. He's my boss.
先签这个切结书吧 如果你们工作时受伤
Sign these stating that if you're injured on the job,
后果自负
it's not our fault.
在办公室工作怎么会受伤呢
How would we injure ourselves in an office?
让我给你们"打个比方"吧
Let me just give you a "for instance."
比方说某些傻妞 例如莎拉
Some girl, let's say her name is Sarah,
在办公室走动
is walking through the office
手中的二号铅笔尖端朝上
with her number 2 pencil facing up-ways.
然后她不小心跌倒了
Well, she trips over her shoes and falls,
然后二号铅笔插穿她的眼球
and that number 2 pencil goes right through her eyeball
直入脑袋
and into her brain.
现在她这辈子就只能靠着用吸管
And now she's gotta eat applesauce through a straw
吃苹果酱维生了
the rest of her life.
像这样就不是我们的错 是她的错
See, that's not our fault, that's her fault,
但剩下就看法官决定
As per the judge's decision
是莎拉·德雷克 还是西船保险公司胜诉了
in Sarah Drake vs. Westship insurance.
先签名 我去叫伊莱
Sign those. I'll get Eli.
谢谢 抱歉 刚才没听清您的名字
Thank you. I'm sorry, I didn't get your name.
因为我压根就没告诉你
That's 'cause I didn't give it to you.
你在干嘛啊
What are you doing?
怎么可以告诉别人真名呢
You never give anybody your real name.
给假名 这样你要是不小心输入错数据
That way, when you make your little data entry mistake,
他们没办法逮到你负责
they can't track the real you down.
你看安然公司的审判 就没抓我去吧
You didn't see me at the Enron trial, did you?
还有你眼中希望的光芒 给我全关掉
And that light in your eyes? Dim it down, way down.
让我看看
Show me.
真不错 你怎么办到的
That's actually really good. How'd you do that?
-我想到了我们的未来 -太棒了
- I thought about our future. - Great!
伊莱在开会
Eli's in a meeting,
但你们得先看这个防治性骚扰的影带
But you gotta watch this sexual harassment video.
看这影带有点浪费时间吧
Watching a video seems like a waste of time
何不让我们先开始干有用的活呢
when we could be doing something more productive.
浪费时间吗 让我给你们"打个比方"吧
A waste of time? Let me just give you a "for instance."
比方说有个多明尼加籍工人
There's this Dominican guy,
他来给办公室换新的桶装水
he's installing a new water jug in the office,
然后他看着一个女性员工说
and he looks at one of the female employees and says,
"说到桶装水"[胸部] 然后他伸出魔爪
"Speaking of jugs," and then he reaches up
抓住了一个员工的胸部
and cups the employee's breastesses
然后开始拧人家乳头之类的事情
then starts twisting on the nips and what have you.
如果是你碰到 你会怎么做呢
Now, how do you handle a situation like that?
我最长的那段感情就是这么开始的呢
That's actually how my longest relationship started.
我也希望给你那升职机会啊 贝弗莉
I'd love to give you that promotion, Beverly,
但在那之前 你得先帮我... 做点事情
But first, you'll have to do something...for me.
别做啊 贝弗莉 别做
Don't do it, Beverly! Don't do it!
剧透警告 我看过这影带了
Spoiler alert. I've watched this in here before,
贝弗莉的下场可不太妙啊
and it does not end well for Beverly.
我不是要怪被害人
Well, not to blame the victim,
但谁没事穿黑胸罩上班啊
but who wears a black bra to work?
这柜子如果能够按字母首排列
These shelves would be so much better
然后再根据颜色排列就能好很多呢
if they were alphabetized and color-coordinated.
别管了 快来看贝弗莉的上层柜子[胸部]
Forget that cabinet and look at the top shelf on Beverly.
我都有点嫉妒她了
I'm a little jelly.
这样就对了 贝弗莉
That's right, Beverly.
现在弯下腰 捡起那文件吧
Now, bend down and pick up that file.
道格你又故技重施了
Oh, Doug, you're up to your old tricks,
但她每次都上钩
and she falls for it every time.
在此暂停一下 然后记下我们从
Let's pause here and write down these rules
贝弗莉与道格影片中学到的规矩
we've learned from Beverly and Doug.
我爱死这里的味道了
Oh, I love the smell in here.
让我想起在华尔街实习的日子
Reminds me of interning on Wall Street,
除了没有尊严与未来的部分之外
you know, minus the dignity and the future.
为什么纸制品会与碳粉盒摆一起啊
But why would the paper products be near the toner cartridges?
当初整理这柜子的人
Whoever organized this place
不是蠢就是懒 或者两者皆是
must have been stupid or lazy or both.
两者皆是
A-both.
别管人家柜子了
Forget all that shelf stuff.
你不是来改善人家办公布局的
You are not here to improve office layout,
你是来保持安静 假装干活
you're here to keep quiet, pretend like you're working,
然后每天工作尾声
and steal five to ten vitamin waters
偷偷从休息室偷五到十瓶维他命水走的
from the break room at the end of each day.
你们是在看黄色影片 还不找我一起看吗
Are you watching dirty videos in here and didn't invite me?
性骚扰影片都出真人3D版了吗
They're making harassment videos in 3-D now?
我刚刚在找新的临时工
I was looking for the new temps,
但好像误入了选美大会啊
but I think I wandered into a beauty pageant.
投票结果出炉了 你们俩平手
Uh, the votes are in. It's a tie.
我是伊莱·格林 办公室经理
I'm Eli Green, the office manager.
你们就是新来的临时工了吧
You must be our new temps.
我是卡洛琳·钱宁
I'm Caroline Channing.
我是卡门·圣地亚哥
And I'm Carmen...Sandiego.
我们没有关系
No relation.
天啊 这太赞了
Oh, my God, this is great!
这猫咪在偷吃狗狗的狗食
The cat's eating the dog's food.
那狗的反应就是"神马"
The dog's just like, "Wha-a-at?"
去查"猫吃狗食"
Yo, psst. "Cat eats dog food."
快去网上看
Youtube it now.
我在忙着干活呢
Kinda busy with my work.
我们拿"最低工资"
It's called "Minimum wage"
就是因为只该做"最少的活"
'cause you're supposed to do the minimum.
今天现做又不用付钱
Coffee tastes so much better
这咖啡味道就是特别棒啊
when it's from today and you haven't paid for it.
那狗的反应就是"神马"
The dog's just like, "Wha-a-at""
太经典了
Classic.
喜欢那影片吗 去查查"猫咪大战一岁娃"
You like that video? Look up "Cat vs. Toddler."
不用谢
You're welcome.
这里是模特公司吗
Is this a modeling agency?
我是不是上错楼层了
Did I get off on the wrong floor?
你要上哪都行 别在这[脱]就行了
I don't care where you get off as long as it's not here.
伊莱 知道他们什么时候决定
Hi, Eli. So any idea when they'll decide
要让谁升职当初级行政主管了吗
who's getting the junior executive promotion, or-
还没 但我刚跟上头的人
Not yet, but I did just mention your name
-提了一下你呢 莱恩 -我是莱昂
- to the big guys, Ryan. - I'm Leon.
你好吗 卡洛琳
Hey, Caroline.
有个问题
Hi. Question:
我已经弄完第一季度的索赔报告了
I already finished the first quarter claim reports...
你嗑药嗑傻啦 我们得做越慢越好
Are you doping? We need to stretch this out.
而且我还有空余时间 我就自己先
And since I had time, I took the liberty
修改了开销表的模板格式
of reformatting the expense template,
接下来你想我干什么呢 伊莱
so what would you like me to do now, Eli?
念我的名字 念我的名字[性爱常见]
Say my name, say my name.
卡洛琳 你不只是人美
Hey, Caroline, you're not just hot,
干活也是没话说啊
You're on fire over there.
你应该去申请一下
You should be throwing your hat
那个行政的职位
in the ring for that executive job.
真的吗
Really?
那女孩的反应就是"神马"
And this girl's just like, "Wha-a-at?"
那上班的地方简直在吞噬灵魂
That temp place is soul-sucking,
我都不知道我还有灵魂可以被吞噬
and I didn't even know I had a soul to suck.
如果那是自杀遗书 记得把我名字加到一起
If that's a suicide note, just add my name to the end.
拜托 没那么坏啦
Come on, it's not that bad,
我喝了四杯免费的新鲜咖啡
and I got four free fresh coffee drinks,
其中一杯还撒有焦糖沫
and one had a caramel drizzle.
焦糖沫
Caramel drizzle?
我下一份临时工的名字就叫这个
That's definitely my name at my next temp job.
我不晓得这会不会变成正式工作
I don't know if this is such a temp job.
我在填申请表
I'm filling out this application
申请初级行政主管的职位
to apply for that junior executive position.
不 不许
Oh, no, you're not.
我们只再回去上一次班
We're only going back one more time
拿够涂改液做
to get enough wite-out
金·卡戴珊的那种全白美甲就走
to do the Kim Kardashian white manicure.
麦克斯 你今天也看见了
Max, you saw me there today.
我很擅长这份工作
I'm good at this,
而且在那上班我感觉很棒
and it felt amazing to be working somewhere
因为我的才能受到重视和支持
where my skills are valued and supported.
难道你在这里就不被支持吗
Are you not feeling supported here?
抱歉 我是你老板 不是你的胸罩
I'm sorry, I'm a boss, not a bra.
我应该多称赞你吗
Should I praise you more?
你最厉害的就是
Really killing it
就是靠在柜台上什么都不干
with the leaning on the counter doing nothing.
厉害啊 卡洛琳 甚好
Kudos, Caroline. Huzzah.
我的"甚好"呢
Hey, where's my "huzzah"?
我刚也光站着什么都不干呀
I was standing around doing nothing too.
别忘了还有我
And don't forget about me.
我是光坐着什么都不干
I was sitting around doing nothing.
在韩国 你们这种人会被扔出街头
In Korea, you all would be left on the curb
等着跟垃圾一起被收走
and taken away with the garbage.
你就是这么被收来美国的吗 阿憨
Is that how you got to America, Han?
厄尔 卡洛琳在犯傻
Earl, Caroline's being an idiot.
我们现在直接当着她面说啊
Oh, are we doing this in front of her now?
如果我告诉你今晚的小蛋糕销售一空
Hey, would you still apply for that job
你还会申请那份工作吗
if I told you we sold out of the cupcakes tonight?
就剩最后一个哦
Last one.
那又怎么样 才好个一天
Oh, so what, they're good one day
你就想我吃回头草啊
and you want me to take them back?
你当我是谁 罗伯特·帕丁森吗
Who am I, Robert Pattinson?
所以你要把小椰子蛋糕踢出你的生活吗
So you just cut lil' coconut here out of your life?
太冷酷无情了
That's cold.
麦克斯 这份工作提供医疗保险
Max, this job offers medical benefits.
连有些医生都没有医疗保险呢
There are doctors who don't have medical benefits.
还有财务保障
And financial security.
或许我不想每天早上都在
Maybe I want to wake up every morning
求自杀的心态中醒来
not wanting to kill myself.
真奇怪 但随便你啦
Well, that's weird, but whatever.
姐可是沃顿商学院毕业的
I went to Wharton.
各位同事 请注意
Pay attention, everyone.
我知道大家工作都非常忙
I know you're all very busy working hard-
恭喜你
Congratulations,
你赢得一台免费的IPAD
you've just won a free ipad.
各位同事 请注意
Attention, everyone!
当我一心工作心无旁骛时
While doing work and nothing but work,
可能不小心下载了一个会喵喵叫的病毒
I may have downloaded a virus that meows,
所以大家要小心哦
so be on the lookout.
请继续 伊莱
Carry on, Eli.
谢谢 卡门
Thank you, Carmen.
很高兴宣布 楼上的高层
Happy to say, tenth floor
终于选出了新一任初级行政主管
has finally picked our new junior exec,
那个人现在就坐着这里
and that person is sitting right here.
-太棒了 -不是你 是卡洛琳
- Yes! - No, Caroline.
-太棒了 -不是吧
- Yes! - No!
我请大家喝香槟
Champagne on me!
太棒了
Yes!
给 我拿了瓶新的
Here, I got us a fresh bottle,
因为我是老板了
'cause I'm the boss.
布莱克小姐 你能帮我把香槟打开吗
Miss Black, would you pop that cork for me?
乐意效劳 钱宁小姐 你个贱人
I'd be happy to, Miss Channing, you bitch.
好了
Okay.
好了好了
Okay, okay,
现在我要好好祝酒[烤土司]
now I'm gonna make a proper toast.
这里怎么弄啊
I don't know how.
他们的烤面包机在咱们厨房里呢
Their toaster oven's in our kitchen.
致麦克斯 我保证不会性骚扰你
To Max--I promise not to sexually harass you
无论作为上司的我有多饥渴
no matter how much I'm required to as your superior.
致卡洛琳 我不能保证不这样对你
To Caroline- I cannot promise the same thing,
因为姐们 你长得还行
'cause sister, you fine.
糟糕 我把香槟洒在我的好外套上了
Oh, crap! I spilled champagne on my good bucket blazer.
就洒在你胸口那吧 贝弗莉
Yes, right there on your breasts, Beverly.
我在扮演性骚扰录像带里的道格
I'm doing Doug from the sexual harassment video.
那个道格吗 你演得真到位
The Doug? Love your harassment work!
尤其是那个被炒鱿鱼后
Especially that sad H.R. scene
你一边可怜啜泣
where you get fired and cry
但还试图稍微"自摸"一下的场景
but still manage to touch yourself a little.
贝弗莉
Wow, Beverly,
你胸部这么大 可能得用掉整盒纸巾
your breasts are so big, I might need the whole box.
够了 感觉被你越擦越脏了
That's enough. You're making this rag feel even dirtier.
-把那个递给我 -什么
- Hey, hand me that. - What?
-我的西船公司新雨披吗 -对
- My new Westship company poncho? - Yep.
现在是我的胸围巾了
Now it's my booze bib.
我爱死这个了
Oh, I love this.
它既小到能装进你的包包
Somehow it's small enough to fit in your purse,
但也大到能在发生
but large enough to sleep under
抗议示威活动时穿着露宿睡觉
during an "Occupy Wall Street"-type situation.
麦克斯 我再给你倒点香槟
Max, I'm pouring you more champagne
因为我有个
because I have something
超级兴奋的消息想告诉你
really exciting I want to tell you.
我跟伊莱说让他把你转成正式工
I talked to Eli about hiring you full-time.
你现在是初级行政主管的行政助理了
You are now a junior executive's executive assistant!
老娘要把你打得趴下
I will knock you to the ground!
麦克斯 好好想想
Max, think about it.
你之后就有医保了
It comes with health care.
你以后就不用在
You wouldn't have to decide
长期避孕药和事后避孕药之间做选择了
between birth control pills and morning-after pills.
你是在剥夺一个女性选择的权利吗
Are you trying to take away a woman's right to choose?
来嘛 会很好玩的
Come on, it could be so fun.
一起上班 喝免费咖啡
Coming to work together, getting free coffee-
好的那种 混合咖啡
the good kind, the blended kind-
更不用说可以影印我们的屁屁
not to mention xeroxing our asses
来感到前所未有的活力
and feeling more alive than ever.
瞧 我来示范下你上司可以多有趣
Watch, I'll show you what a fun boss I can be.
我们一起来影印屁屁吧
Let's xerox our asses.
我怎么能拒绝复制我的屁屁呢
Well, how could I say no to copying my butt?
这世界上唯一比我的屁股还棒的
The only thing better than one of my butts
就是两个我的屁股
is two of my butts.
-我先来 -你晚了一步
- I'll go first. - Too late!
你想要法律尺寸纸张 还是三孔打洞机纸张
Do you want legal size paper or three-hole punch?
"三孔打洞"
Three-hole punch?
我最长那段感情就是这么结束的
That's how my longest relationship ended.
你个出卖灵魂给公司的家伙 动手吧
Ready, you corporate sell-out. Fry me.
为什么它还在闪呢
Hey, why is it still flashing?
我点的是复印100份 而不是一份
I put in 100 copies instead of one.
别担心 可以留着圣诞节当卡片用
Don't worry about it, we'll use them as christmas cards.
瞧 所以我才要个助理嘛
See? That's why I need an assistant.
谢谢 但我不打算接受这份白痴工作
Thanks, but I'm not gonna take this stupid corporate job.
我会继续坚持做小蛋糕 即使你放弃了
I'm gonna stick with cupcakes, even though you just quit.
我没有放弃蛋糕生意
I didn't quit the cupcake business.
你应该记得 是它放弃了我们
If you remember, it quit us.
至少干这份工作有意义
At least this job makes sense.
你每个月有固定的收入 福利
You get a regular paycheck, benefits.
你不必花整整两年的时间
You don't spend two whole years of your life
倾尽所有
giving it everything,
然后像个失败者那样转身离开
and then walk away feeling like a failure.
快下来
Get off that now.
我担心你的屁股会得癌症
I'm worried you're giving yourself butt cancer.
等等 你觉得自己是失败者吗
Wait, you think you're a failure?
我怎么觉得我们很棒
'cause I think we did amazing.
蛋糕店倒闭了 麦克斯
The shop closed, Max.
我们的梦想当着我们的爆了
Our dream blew up in our face.
很多东西都会当着你的面"爆出来"
Lots of things blow up in your face.
这是女人生命的一部分
It's part of being a woman.
你只需用毛巾擦干净 然后走人
You just... towel off and keep going.
你真的要留在这里工作吗
You're really going to do this?
这本来是在我们重拾蛋糕梦之前
This was just supposed to be a temporary distraction
暂时来打发时间挣房租的
till we got back to the cupcake thing.
不 麦克斯 蛋糕梦才是临时的工作
No, Max. Cupcakes were the temp job.
不 蛋糕梦是我们的梦想
No, cupcakes were our dream.
我以前错了
Well, I was wrong.
或许人没有梦想更好
Maybe it's better not to have a dream.
早上好 各位
Good morning, everyone.
伊莱 听说你要我进来找你呀
Eli, they said you wanted to see me in here?
钱宁小姐 我叫易·米歇尔 人事部的
Ms. Channing, my name is Michelle Yi, I'm with H.R.
这是我的正式欢迎会吗
Aw! Is this my official welcome?
你好
Oh, hello.
来 我买了一些
Well, here, I brought Some
入职面包圈和原味奶油乳酪
first-day bagels and plain cream cheese.
香葱味的话 嘴巴会容易有味道
Sometimes chives can be a little breathy, am I right?
是这个女人性骚扰你吗
Is this the woman who sexually harassed you?
对 就是她
Yup, that's her.
这个好 真搞笑
Oh, good one! Really funny.
我会骚扰你吗
Me harassing you?
拜托 你根本不是我的菜
Come on, you're not even my type.
卡洛琳 这不是闹着玩的
Caroline, this isn't a joke.
相信我 我已经经历过四次了
Trust me, I've been through four of these.
慢着 这是怎么回事
Wait, what's going on?
钱宁小姐 请别直接跟卡门说话
Ms. Channing, please don't address Carmen directly.
-麦克斯 -"大大"
- Max. - "Max"?
那是她给你取的爱称吗 卡门
Is that a pet name she has for you, Carmen?
是的 她还叫我"焦糖沫"
Yes. She also calls me "Caramel drizzle."
你能告诉我昨晚跟钱宁小姐
Can you tell me what exactly happened
到底发生什么事吗
With ms. Channing last night?
她抚摸我的胸部
She fondled my breasts.
易小姐 事实不是这样
Ms. Yi, it's not how it sounds.
我们当时在喝酒 我假装成男人
We were drinking, and I was pretending to be a man.
"喝酒" "假装成男人"
"Drinking." "Pretending to be a man."
别写这个 别这这个
Don't write that down. Don't write that down.
卡门 当钱宁小姐摸你时
And Carmen, when Ms. Channing touched you,
你有什么感觉
how did that make you feel?
下流肮脏
Dirty.
下流 薪水过低
Dirty and underpaid.
她觉得下流
She felt dirty?
拜托 易小姐 你不了解她
Come on, Ms. Yi, you don't know her.
她最下流了
She's the dirty girl.
她就是个肮脏下流的女孩
She is a dirty, dirty girl.
那会让你感觉性奋吗
And does that turn you on?
不会 我根本不会性奋
No! It's almost impossible to turn me on.
幸好 现在我感觉没那么糟了
Oh, good. Now I don't feel so bad.
相信我 她在捏造事实
Trust me, she's making this stuff up.
抱歉 钱宁小姐
I'm sorry, Ms. Channing.
我们不得不解雇你
We're gonna have to terminate your employment.
这太离谱了
This is outrageous!
她说的都是假的
Nothing she said ever happened.
那你怎么解释这个
Then how do you explain this?
这份复印件出自一台
That is a copy from a xerox machine
急需碳粉的影印机
badly in need of toner,
如果我当上了这里的主管
which is just one of the many oversights
这种玩忽职守的事情
that would not have continued
就绝对不会发生
had I been made an executive here.
再见
Good day.
我不知道她在说什么
I don't know what she's talking about.
那个屁股哪需要什么碳粉[超紧致]
That butt couldn't be any toner.
这句写下 快写下
Write that down, write that down.
能给我看一眼吗
Can I get a peek at that?
今晚心情如何 卡洛琳
How are you tonight, Caroline?
愤怒 沮丧 丢脸
Angry, frustrated, humiliated.
餐厅每个周二的普通心情
Just another tuesday at the diner.
你好 卡门
Hello, Carmen.
还是我该叫你"焦糖沫"
Or is it "Caramel drizzle?"
让我告诉你
Just so you know,
这场闹剧会上我的职业工作记录
that stunt will go on my professional work record.
拜托
Oh, please.
这家餐馆才会上你的职业工作记录
This diner's on your professional work record.
你的记录干净得很 伊莱删掉了
And your record's clean. Eli expunged it
因为我给了他几张我屁股的复印件
because I gave him a couple of my ass xeroxes.
他把那图塑封起来 要当餐垫用
He's laminating them and using them as place mats.
我的主意
My idea.
麦克斯 你为什么要害我被解雇
For what, Max? Why'd you get me fired?
我为什么要害你被解雇
Why'd I get you fired?
那让我打个比方来说吧
Well, let me give you a "for instance."
我以前认识个女孩 她从不言败
I once knew this girl who was so used to not failing
而在她第一次失败后
that the first time she did,
她吓坏了 她忘了自己是谁
she got so scared, she forgot who she was
并试图想成为别人
and tried to be somebody else,
然后她就摸我的胸部
And then she touched my breastesses.
如果你不想
Look, it's cool if you don't
加入蛋糕梦也没关系
want to join in on the cupcake dream,
但至少你要找到别的梦想
but at least wait till you find another.
别天上掉什么 你都扑过去
Don't hop on the first one that comes along.
这是梦想 不是男人
It's a dream, not a man.
看吧 你果然下流
See? You are a dirty girl.
我是个肮脏下流的女孩
I'm a dirty, dirty girl.
蛋糕放弃者
Hey, cupcake quitters.
看 你们害我沦落到什么地步了
Look, do you see what you've driven me to?
超市蛋糕
Supermarket cakes.
苏菲 你不用吃那个
Sophie, you don't need to eat those.
你可以吃我们做的
You can have one of ours.
麦克斯自制小蛋糕重新开张了
Max's homemade cupcakes is back in business.
如果你骗我 那就太残忍了
It would be cruel to kid me.
不会 我们这次要换个方式来
Nope. We're doing it differently this time.
是吗 什么方法
We are? How?
我也不知道
I have no idea.
但首先
But for starters,
我任命你为我的新行政主管行政助理
you're my new junior executive executive's assistant.
老娘要把你打得趴下
I will knock you to the ground.
老娘现在心花开呀
Well, mama happy now.